>> Jem Young: 最终项目。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: The final projects.
要做到这一点，我们需要了解 Web 套接字是什么。
To do that we need to understand
what a web socket is.
什么是 Web 套接字 ?
What is a web socket?
嗯。
Yes.
>> 扬声器 2: 您可以从客户机使用它来打开长期连接，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You can use it from the
client to open a long-lived connection,
你只会把讯息传达给服务器
and you just push messages back and
forth, client to server.
这是两分多路复用
It's two way and multiplexed.
> > Jem Young: 我不知道你是否读了这条指令，但这完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I don't know if you read
the instruction, but that's exactly right.
这是客户机与服务器之间的持久双向连接。
It's a persistent bidirectional
connection between the client and server.
不像目前使用 TCP的现状
So unlike the current status quo with TCP,
每个连接都需要握手
which every single connection
requires that handshake.
通过已移交的 Web 套接字，您只能建立一个连接
With the handed off web socket,
you only make one connection and
它把它保持在隧道里
it keeps that alive through a tunnel.
因此，客户机可以发送数据，服务器可以发送数据，并且
So that way the client can send data,
the server can send data, and
它比 TCP 连接快得多，即使它通过 TCP 运行也是如此。
it's much faster than a TCP connection,
even though it runs over TCP.
故事的道德性是网络套接字是这个持续存在的
The moral of the story,
is the web socket is this persistent
可以发送流数据的连接。
connection that we can
send streaming data.
在聊天的时候用的很多都是你知道的
It's used a lot in chat applications
things like that where you know for
客户机将保持与服务器的通信。
a fact the client is gonna keep
communicating with the server.
所以，为什么不只是保持联系呢 ?
So why not just keep that connection open.
我们以前做的就是这个长轮询的概念，打开了一个 TCP
What we used to do was this concept
of long polling, which was open a TCP
连接，并使其保持活动状态，并不断地不断地推送数据。
connection, and just keep it alive and
just keep pushing data back and forth.
如果客户机保持打开状态，服务器将保持打开状态。
And that way the client stays open,
the server stays open.
没问题但这和网站的效率不一样
It's fine, but
it's not as efficient as web sockets.